krantcents.com 2017-05-29

# Privacy Policy

We take your privacy seriously.

What This Privacy Policy Covers:

Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.

Information Collection and Use

When you post a comment on the site, we ask for your name, email address, website URL.

Log Files

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocal) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

This blog uses Google Analytics, wp-stats to automatically receive and record information from your browser, including your IP address, cookie information, and the page you request.

Cookies and Web Beacons

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

We also use third party advertisements to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites). Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. You may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

Information Sharing and Disclosure

I will not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies.Data like your email address will not be made visible on the site, unless you choose to display it.

Changes to this Privacy Policy

I may update this policy. In the event that this happens a prominent notice a prominent notice will be made on this site.

If you have any questions, please contact me.

Thanks,

Krantcents.
